Hello friends, in today's video we are going to learn
about accidental insurance
which is available on the phone app, you are going to get
great benefits from many companies on this,
so let's quickly
understand this accidental insurance
easily, hello friends my name is
Rahul and you are watching, understand easily
friends, if I talk about accidental insurance, then the
way the insurance company gives you the plan here is two
conditions, that if something is lost in either of the two,
then they pass the plan, so the first
condition is that if the person has
taken insurance under this scheme, if he dies
due to an accident, then
his head or the nominee will get the
full amount and whatever amount he had taken out in that
accidental insurance, he will
get it completely normally, the second condition
is where the person did not die
but due to the accident, any part of his body becomes
permanently disabled, if I
talk about it quite simple, then suppose due to the
accident, his hand which is now forever  If the head
is amputated or the legs are amputated, then
in this situation, because that body part has become
permanently disabled, then in this situation, the
insurance companies also
give complete clarity to that particular person.
So, in today's video, the insurance that we are going to
talk about is
available on the phone, so let's quickly go to the phone, let's go to
my mobile screen
and I will
explain to you the complete details of this accidental insurance there. So
friends, now we have come to the screen of my phone, so
now we
open the app on the phone. As soon as
you open it on the phone,
you will see a symbol below which it is
written My Money, you have to
click here. As soon as you click here, there is
a section of insurance
inside which there is an icon of accident and it
is written Accident, so we will
click on Accident. As soon as we
click on Accident, then all the details of their plan will be
visible to you here. Before seeing this plan, you can ask a question on the
top right hand side here.  If we
look at Maa ka Sai,
first of all we were clicking here,
after clicking on the side of this question mark, you will
see a lot of questions related to this policy, so
if you want to know the answer to any question, then
you have to click on the relevant question,
as soon as you click on the question,
its answer will be visible to you here,
if you still have some doubt, then there is a
box like contact us below,
you have to click on it and as soon as you open
that topic, you will see here that the
page will open in this way where
you
can ask any question related to the policy here and after that if you send it, then
you will get the related answer on the phone, for
now we are tired
and here we have again come to the main page, then
you will see that here three
types of planning are available, we
start from the bottom, the first one is Planet, that is
Rs.24  It is of Rs. 1000 in which
Rs. 1000 will be given in the fort, the second plan
is of Rs. 120 in which Rs. 5 will be given
and the third plan which is said to be a popular
plan, then Rs. 40 will have to be paid and in which Rs. 20 will be
given in the plan, the validity of all these three
plans is Rs. 1000,
Nitin plant which will be valid till the end,
now if you want any plant then you will have to
select it on this plan,
suppose I have a plant of that plant, then
I will click here, then this tomato of
green color will come next to the tweet, for
now we will complete the analysis
that I feel that Rs. 480
is more beneficial because 2004 simultaneous claims will be
much better, so click on positive
and after that after getting the
policy, a button is given below, so
you have to click here, like above the get policy, the
page opens, so you
can see here, friends, first of all it is
written ICICI Lombard, so this
From the policy that you buy, or the policy with this number
that you are getting, there is a
benefit below it as well, so we do it here,
as if we click on the benefit, it is
written here that benefits are
included, so this plan gives two benefits,
first of all we open the benefit,
here it is written cover for death
resulting from accident, so here
any person who has taken insurance,
if he dies, then
his nominee or legal heir will get Rs 2011 in the fort,
now
here their next condition says that the
death that happened during the accident should be
in total, to hell means at the
time when the plan is taken, then if the jewellery of the plan gets damaged in an accident
inside that diamond, only then the
plan benefit will be
available, after this friends, there is
no waiting period for this in any way, that is, the
policy will become active on the day you take the policy, after this, the
second benefit is opened, then  It is
written here that cover for permanent
total disability resulting from
accident, so here the person
who has taken this policy does not die,
but his body parts which are completely
intact get damaged, that is, hand,
leg, if in an
accident, if the leg of someone
who had taken the policy gets cut, then tell him that a
compensation amount of ₹120 will be given, the other
two points are that whatever is the time of accident offer, do not
give dual policy
term, there should not be
any waiting period in the policy taken and the
policy will become
active from the day a person takes the policy, now if
we want back, then here you
can see that after these benefits,
like Sameshwar, if I bring it from poverty, then
accordingly the amount of Rs.20 is being
shown as SMS, after this, its relative
value will come in the phone as you log in, then
you can edit and it will come here, like on the full moon,
Rahu, Cancer, my name, after this  I have an
email id and after that you
can see the date of birth, it is written below the date of birth
that the age should be between 10 and
65 years, so the center clearly told that the
minimum age for taking the policy is 65 years
and the maximum age is 65 years,
if it is more than that then you will not be able to take the policy,
after this friends there is nominee,
now if I click on nominee then
inside nominee you will see that you will get different
options, so you have to keep this as nominee also,
you can keep it normally, for now I
use this here, after nominee you have to
enter the nominee and
after that I agree to the terms
and conditions, so first of all
we click on the terms and conditions here, as if you will
click on terms and conditions, then
you will see a lot of terms and conditions here,
friends, just to take insurance on them,
if you actually take any insurance then first of all all
its terms and conditions  It is very important to read the terms and conditions to
take this policy, so here also there are a
lot of terms and conditions,
but read all these terms and conditions of that,
if you have decided to take this policy then first of all
you must read the entire terms and conditions, we will
cover the up and down here, now you can see
after agree, in the bottom left hand side,
you have written the arm hole of this plan by ₹40,
after that I
click on the small i button, as soon as
I click, then
you will get to see the breakup of the premium amount here,
so you can see the premium which is
406 point to 0407, which this insurance company
is charging and after that the
integrated gst along with it which is ₹93
which will go to the house and in this way the
cross premium gets rounded off and becomes flat, so
you have got the complete
breakup here also, when friends, you will
fill all these details now, then after that whatever
option of pay,  The height will be automatically
highlighted, so you
can pay your amount by just clicking on it. You
can do it through Quit on the phone or you can make payment through debit
card, credit card and other different means. I
hope that
you have understood all the information that I have provided you.
If you still have any
doubts, you can definitely ask by commenting. I am grateful to you
for watching the video and giving your time.